Guide to the Michael Anania Papers circa 1950s-2006
University of Chicago Library
- Series V: Manuscripts by Others
  - Kleinzahler, August, 1972-1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Klinkowitz, Jerome, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Knoepfle, John, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Krysl, Marilyn, "Ghazals for the Turn of the Century," 1997 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Kuzma, Greg, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Leider, Emily, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Leswick, Henry, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Lieberman, Laurence, Unassigned Frequencies: Whispers Out of Time, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Lieberman, Laurence, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Llewellyn, John, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Lojeck, Kimberly, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Lourie, Dick, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Lowenfels, Walter, The Metallurgical Process, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Major, Clarence, Not Such Unearthly Stones as I Feel, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Martin, Isabel, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Matthias, John, Beltane at Aphelion: Longer Poems, circa 1990 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Matthias, John, "A Compostella Diptych," undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Matthias, John, Cuttings, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Matthias, John, "Double Derivation, Association, & Cliché: from The Great Tournament Roll of Westminster," undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Matthias, John, "Facts From an Apocryphal Midwest," undated (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Matthias, John, "Five Cuttings with Endeavors & Repeated Incantation," undated (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Matthias, John, A Gathering of Ways, undated (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Matthias, John, Pages: From a Book of Years, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Matthias, John, Places, Poems, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Matthias, John, Places, Poems, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Matthias, John, "Places and Poems: A Self-Reading and a Reading of the Self in the Romantic Context from Wordsworth to Parkman," undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Matthias, John, Selected Poems, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Matthias, John, Selected Poems, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Matthias, John, "Six for Michael Anania," undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Matthias, John, "Thirty-Nine Among the Sands, His Steps," undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Matthias, John, Turns, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Matthias, John, Unpublished Poems, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Matthias, John, "Working Progress, Working Title [Automystifstical Plaice]", undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Matthias, John, 1979-1989 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Matthias, John, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Matthias, John, 1985-1988 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Mazza, Cris, Girl Beside Him, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Mazza, Cris, Girl Beside Him, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - McCord, Howard, Perfecting an Unspeakable Act, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - McGrath, Tom, All But the Last, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - McGrath, Tom, All But the Last, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - McGrath, Tom, All But the Last, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - McKernan, John, Is This Nebraska?, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - McKernan, John, "A Poem by John McKernan to Ralph Wardle," 1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - McMahon, Lynne, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - McManus, Jim, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - McMichael, James, Four Good Things, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - McMichael, James, The Last Distance, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - McMichael, James, The Lover’s Familiar, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - McMichael, James, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - McPherson, R. Bruce, Disputing the Passage, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - McPherson, R. Bruce, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Mecklenburger, Ralph, In Search of the Rhyme, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Metcalf, Paul, Apalache, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Michelson, Peter, I Lost it in Sri Lanka, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Michelson, Peter, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Middleton, Christopher, The Lonely Suppers of W.V. Balloon, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Miller, J.L., Autobiography, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., Dream Crutches and the Man of Black Light: Poems, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., Grasses Standing: Selected Poems, 1972-1998, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., Grasses Standing: Selected Poems, 1972-1998, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., A Man to His Shadows, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., Night Road, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., "The Notebooks of David Ignatow," 1971 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., Sky Swept, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., Someone Might Say: Poems, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., tel-let, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., A Window in the Air, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., 1992-1995 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Montague, John, "Home Again," 1971 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Moon, Samuel, Thoughts While Swimming, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Moon, Samuel, Water Eye, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Morley, Hilda, Cloudless at First, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Morley, Hilda, Cloudless at First, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Morley, Hilda, Cloudless at First, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Morley, Hilda, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Morris, Catherine Browder, "Lights From a Farmhouse," undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Morris, Richard, Reno, Nevada, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Moyer, Jennifer, Traveling With Coyotes, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Moyer, Jennifer, When Girls Were Girls, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Moyer, Jennifer, Yeast, 1978-1983 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Moyer, Jennifer, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Müller-Bergh, Klaus, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Murphy, Kay, Belief is Getting More Difficult, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Nash, Jay Robert, "Heads, Hard and Soft," 1968 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Nhuong, Huynh Quang, "The Family’s Secret Move," undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Nhuong, Huynh Quang, "My Ethics Teacher and His Wife," undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Nhuong, Huynh Quang, "My Father Was Mad at My Brother," undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Nhuong, Huynh Quang, "My Old Schoolteacher," undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Nhuong, Huynh Quang, "Water Jug," undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Nhuong, Huynh Quang, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Nicholson, "The Saga of the Son of Sam: ‘History has many cunning passages and contrived corridors," undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Nystrom, Jan, "The Young Lady Who Fell From a Star," undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - O’Connor, Michael Patrick, "The Eighteenth of Brumaire: The Sixth of May," undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - O’Connor, Michael Patrick, "The First Fruits," 1971 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - O’Connor, Michael Patrick, "Pandary," undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - O’Connor, Michael Patrick, 1971-1977 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Odelius, Kristy, Strange Trades, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Odelius, Kristy, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Odell, Jere, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Offen, Ron, "The Chicago Convention: From media to Massage," undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - O’Hara, Frank, Audit, 1959-1964 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - O’Leary, Peter, Watchfulness, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Oringer, Judith, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Pacelli, Martha, Easy Street, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Pastan, Linda, A Perfect Circle of Sun, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Pastan, Linda, undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Peacher, Georgiana, Wanda Norstrom’s African Diary: 1937 & 7, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Pease, Deborah, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Peck, John, Petitio, Repetitio, Agensay, Agengrownde, Matthias, undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Perloff, "Postmodernism and the Crisis of Lyric," undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Pinsky, Robert, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Plath, Sarah, Heating and Cooling, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Plath, Sarah, The Salesman, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, Breathing in Winters, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, Home/Bass, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, Hornman, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, The Mojo Hands Call, I Must Go, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, Ornate With Smoke, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, Untitled, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, Untitled, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, Untitled, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, Velvet B-Bop Kente Cloth, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Plumpp, Sterling, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Potter, Matthew, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Printz-Påhlson, Göran, "The Canon of Literary Modernism: A Note on Abstraction in the Poetry of Erik Lindegren," undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Rago, Maria Christine, The Selected Poems of Henry Rago, 1915-1969, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Rago, Maria Christine, The Selected Poems of Henry Rago, 1915-1969, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Reiss, James, Poems by James Reiss, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Riley, Denise, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Rosen, Aaron, Traces, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Rosen, Aaron, Traces, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Russell, Lawrence, "Magic Juice," 1971 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Schmidt, Michael and Edward Kissam, Aztec Poems, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Schmitz, Dennis, First Snow, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Schmitz, Dennis, The Stranger in the Woods, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Scott, Jr., Nathan A. and William R. kenan, Jr., "The Poetry of Ammons," undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Seelye, John, Lines of Thought: Triangulations in American Art, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Seelye, John, A Territory of the Mind, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Shapiro, David, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Shapiro, Karl, Selected Poems, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Sheehan, Donald and David Keller, Starting Points, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Shepherd, Reginald, Angel, Interrupted, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Shepherd, Reginald, Some Are Drowning, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Shepherd, Reginald, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Sherry, Vincent, "From the Twenties to the Nineties: Pound, Beerbohm, and the Making of Mauberley," 1993 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Sheffield, Elisabeth, "Sugar Smacks," undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Shukovsky, Eileen, Zen Tech, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Shukovsky, Eileen, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Simic, Charles, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Ken, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Sommers, Stephanie, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Starbuck, George and Kathy, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Stelmach, Marjorie Herweg, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Stern, Frederick C., undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Stokes, Terry, "Dining Out in Zurich," undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Stryk, Lucien, Twelve Death Poems of the Chinese Zen Masters, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Stryk, Lucien, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Sward, Robert, undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Tobias, Robert, Our Human Condition: Wrestling with Finality and Mystery, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Trammell, Robert, Famous Men, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Trimble, Mary, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Turner III, Frederick W., undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - VanderMolen, Robert, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Wallenstein, Barry, About the Trouble Not About the Crime, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Walton, James, undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Watson, Debra, undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Webb, Don, Uncle Ovid’s Exercise Book, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Webb, Don, Uncle Ovid’s Exercise Book, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Webb, Igor, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Weinberger, Eliot, Nineteen Ways of Looking at Weng Wei: How a Chinese Poem is Translated, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Wheeler, Susan, La Fontaine’s Wig, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - White, Jackie, Dissertation "The Chameleon’s House," 2004 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Wiegner, Kathleen, What Every Woman Should Know, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Wildman, Eugene, "Coast of Chicago," undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Wildman, Eugene, Looking for the Silk King, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Wildman, Eugene, Looking for the Silk King, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Wildman, Eugene, "Murasaki’s Lover," undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Wildman, Eugene, "Next Time You See Me," undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Wildman, Eugene, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Worth, Douglas, Of Earth: Poems 1964-1974, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Wright, Charles, Cutlines, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Wright, Charles, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Articles and Offprints, 1965-2006 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Articles and Offprints, 1965-2006 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Articles and Offprints, 1965-2006 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Articles and Offprints, 1965-2006 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Articles and Offprints, 1965-2006 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Articles and Offprints, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts, Invitation to the Desert, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts, 1994-2001 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Newspaper Clippings, Publications and Oversize
  - Book Reviews, 1973-1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Book Reviews, 1973-1993 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Color of Dust, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Color of Dust, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Events, 1973-1976 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Events, 1973-1976 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - The Floating Bear, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - General, 1966-1974 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Heat Lines, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - In Natural Light, 1999-2001 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - In Plain Sight, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Journals and Publications, 1967-1974 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Journals and Publications, 1976-1983 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Journals and Publications, 1990-1993 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - The Little Magazine in America: A Modern Documentary History, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - New Poetry Anthology, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - New Poetry Anthology, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - "The Poetry Project Newsletter," 1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - The Pushcart Prize V: Best of the Small Presses, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - The Pushcart Prize V: Best of the Small Presses, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - The Red Menace, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - The Red Menace, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Riversongs, 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Riversongs, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Set/Sorts, undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - The Sky at Ashland, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Small Press Review, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Turnings, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1972-1993 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers, 1959-1995 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers, 1971-1976 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, 1977-1979 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers, 1980-1985 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers, 1986-1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers, 1991-2003 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - The Red Menace, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Samizdat, 1999-2002 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Whole COSMEP Catalog, One Time Supplement to the Directory of Little Magazines and Small Presses, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Events (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Illinois (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Writings by Anania (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Writings by Others (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Others (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Series VII: Audio-Visual
  Series VII, Audio-Visual material is restricted due to the condition of the material or need for special equipment. Select material reformatted – for access SEE Audio-Visual Reformatted Collection.
  - Cassette; Anania Lecture, Raymond Federman Reading, 1982; BBC, Borges at 80, Intro and Narration, Norman Thomas di Giovanni, undated; Carlos Fuentes, University of Illinois Circle Campus, 1982 (2 cassettes) (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Cassette; Chicago Poets Onstage, Mills/Mueller/Anania/Brooks, 1981 (2 cassettes)--This piece has been reformatted SEE Audio-Visual Reformatted Collection; Chicago’s Authors Celebrate Chicago, undated (2 cassettes), This item has been reformatted for access. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Cassette; Conversations with Chicago Writers, Michael Anania, 1981; Dialogue "Poets and Poetry in Chicago," Guest, Michael Anania; Discussion about David Ireland with Cathy, undated; Extension 720, 100 Great Novels, Stern, Anania, 1998; Extension 720, Modern Literature, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Cassette; Extension 720, Mystery Writer, Parker, Anania, Wolfe, 1997; Extension 720, Poetry, undated; Extension 720, Poetry, 2003; Extension 720, Poetry, Anania, Roeske, Payson, Nesbilt, 1997; Extension 720, Poetry of the 20th Century, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Cassette; The Great Chicago Poetry Reunion, WFMT, May 1981 (5 cassettes) (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Cassette; The Great Chicago Poetry Reunion, WFMT, May 1981 (2 cassettes); Interview with Michael and Review of The Red Menace, Writing Chicago with G. Neusenic WBEZ, October 1984; Interview with Readings, KIWR, Iowa Public Radio, October 1992; Ken Smith, Eddie’s Other Live, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Cassette; Michael Anania and Ken Smith, WFMT, 1983; Michael Anania, The Red Menace, undated; Michael Anania, Riversongs, Studs Terkel WTMT 1979; Michael Anania, WBEZ Interview Writing Chicago, undated; Michael Melford, Jethro Burns, Venuti, McPartland, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Cassette; National Radio Theatre, Illinois Sampler, undated; New Premises, undated; Shapiro Interview, undated; Spanish/English, Four Poems, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Cassette; Studs Terkel with Michael Anania, The Red Menace, WFMS, 1986 (2 cassettes); Tribute to Thomas McGrath, Studs Terkel with Alice McGrath, Reginald Gibbons and Michael Anania, 1993 (2 cassettes) (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Compact Disc; Anania at Union League Club H., undated; Raymond Federman’s Take it or Leave It as read by the author, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Record Album; The Holidays from Cold Turkey, a book of poems by Mac Hammond, read by Mac Hammond, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Video; Four Poets Night, undated; Illinois Reads: Talks With Illinois Authors, Featured Author: Michael Anania, The Library Cable Network, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Video; Poetry and Print, 1993 (2 copies); Rainbow Bridges: An Illinois Walk-about #4, Featured Author: Michael Anania, The Library Cable Network, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Video; Twentieth Century Voices, Six Nobel Prize Writers, Boris Pasternak, undated; Wasser, Wind und Manitou: Die Grossen Seen Nordamerikas (2 copies), undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Series VIII: Restricted
  Series VIII, Restricted, contains financial and student material. Folders 6, 10, and 11 will not be open for research until 2081. All other folders will not be open for research until 2049.
  - Audit, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Grant and Fellowship Applications, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Grants, 1971-1996 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Illinois Center for the Book, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1989-2001 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Northwestern University Press, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Partisan Review German Issue, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Read Illinois, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Student Dissertation, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Student Paper, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - The Unit for Contemporary Literature and the Dalkey Archive, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - University of Illinois Press, 1978-1999 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Year of the Young Reader Gala, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 14)